(We Get Along Pretty Well)
- It's good to see you. - Good to see you.
Gosh, Sung Hwan...
is clearly flaunting to have been to Kazakhstan.
- What kind of style is this? - It's pretty.
- It looks good, right? - Yes.
My shoes and hat are Kazakh traditional.
- Gosh, but... Hold on. - Yes?
A lot of fur falls out from this.
From all over... This is driving me crazy.
It's going into my mouth too. My goodness.
(Taking a glance)
Wait. Please don't come close.
- It'll stick on me. - Oh, you're right.
(Wiping it clean)
- I lint-rolled my coat. - Right, this...
Hey, you're quite cold.
(I'm joking.)
By the way, I heard amazing news from Kazakhstan.
Gosh, our President Jun...
won the Grand Award at KBS!
- Thank you. - Congratulations.
("Jun Hyun Moo's Moving Grand Award Win")
Congratulations.
- We have another good news. - What is it?
Brother, do a high-five with me.
- My Pepper Brother. - My Pepper Brother.
Our war isn't over.
- What? - I mean...
- Oh, the Best Couple Award? - The Best Couple Award.
You were nominated for the Best Couple Award.
Thankfully, us, Pepper Brothers...
were nominated for the Best Couple Award.
You can vote until midnight today,
- so please vote for us, - Pepper Brothers.
Pepper Brothers.
- You look good together. - Please vote for us.
(Smiling)
(Our Sweet Little Family)
The weather isn't nice.
(Kian84 came to the airport while showing off his Japanese skills.)
You're studying hard.
So, it's not very good.
(Trudging while commenting on the cloudy day)
Where are you going?
I went there to pick someone up.
(Looking around)
Mom!
- Mom! - Oh, it's your mom.
- Oh, she came from Jeju. - Yes.
You must be hungry.
(Whenever Kian84 visits Jeju Island, )
(she prepares a feast for him as he's working hard.)
Goodness.
(She always cares for her son sincerely.)
- Mother... - Be careful.
(A sweet mom who cheers Kian84 on right by his side)
- Bye, Mom. - I'm leaving. Bye.
It's Madam Yoon Kyung Mi's...
sixty...
(Thinking)
It's her 65th birthday,
so I went to pick her up.
Mom!
(Mom, come over to this side.)
- It's still red light. - Right.
(Staring into the distance after awkwardly calling her)
Oh, you haven't seen your mom yet?
It was awkward to keep looking at her...
- after saying hi. - Oh, is that so?
After I went, "Mom..."
It's hard for only sons to stare intently at their moms.
- Is that so? - "Hi." And we'd look elsewhere.
Who does that? Why do you keep...
When you see your mom across the street,
do you keep smiling at her while looking?
- Yes. When you see... - I don't do that, but...
your mom and dad, don't you go like this?
- "Mom!" - That's why you need a daughter.
(This is why you need a daughter like Joy in this world.)
Sons can't do that.
(The only son only looks at the ground instead of his mom.)
(Rushing)
- Gosh, it's so heavy. - What's that?
- Goodness. - What did you bring?
Your face...
- What? - You look so worn out.
- What? - You don't look so good.
(You don't look so good.)
What does that mean?
- It's my first time hearing it. - "It's bad."
It's a Gyeongsang Province dialect.
- It's from Gyeongsang Province? - It is.
It means it's not so good.
- I just learned it. - "It's bad?"
Then what about when she told you that?
(What about when his mom told him that?)
- He didn't listen. - Right.
I don't listen to her much.
When our moms talk,
we'd get the gist of it...
and don't ask about the unimportant stuff.
Because the conversation gets long.
- Why did you pack so much? - I mean...
I brought green onion kimchi. I made some kimchi.
I have lots of kimchi at home.
There's something on your face.
Here?
You do things like that too?
I do that.
(Staring)
You look so rough.
- What? - You didn't wash your face?
- I did. - You washed your face?
- She knows him well. - I did in the morning.
Okay.
(Running away to the taxi that arrived just in time)
Should I put this in there too?
- It should be placed upright. - Why?
- It should be placed upright. - This?
This doesn't have to be upright.
- But this one should be. - I'll get in first.
(I'll get in first.)
- Goodness. - Hello.
(He sets off with his mom in a taxi.)
You look so rough.
- What? - Your face...
(Her son's skin keeps drawing her attention even in the taxi.)
- How many times has it been? - Your face...
It's all right.
You should apply some cream.
It's rough because I'm old.
- No, it's not. Your face... - It's okay.
It's so funny because it hits close to home.
(Don't eat flour-based food.)
(Be careful.)
(Diabetes is a chronic disease.)
You should take care of your skin too.
- Well, I... - You're still single.
You shouldn't look like that.
I've seen a dermatologist a few times,
but it doesn't change much.
But still...
Your skin ages in no time.
You're a lot older now.
That wasn't a rap, was it?
I thought she was a rapper.
Please drop a beat.
You can't just go once.
You need to see one continuously.
A single man should have...
- She's starting. - shiny skin...
to meet ladies.
- She passed. - She'd get a pass for that.
The producers would get intimidated instead.
(Because she's so talented)
You should apply some cream. Other people...
have shiny skin.
What?
- You need to put on some cream. - Okay.
(A nag-like rap filled with motherly love)
Normally, when moms keep nagging like that,
children would go, "Stop!"
- I do too. - But you don't.
- I think of it as her folk song. - Is that so?
- It's a folk song? - That's right.
When we were young,
we talked back to everything like it's "100 Minute Debate."
It's pointless.
Moms must say whatever they want.
- You can't stop them. - You can't.
- If you refute, she refutes too. - Yes, it keeps going.
"Okay." That's the best answer.
(Quick acceptance is the way.)
- You didn't have breakfast at all? - No.
I felt rushed in the morning.
I cried a bit while looking at Candy's photos.
The dog.
"Candy, when I bring your younger siblings,"
"treat them well so they wouldn't hurt."
I kept praying to Candy like that.
Well...
The dog we had, Candy...
Has it been 13 years?
We adopted the dog when I was 30.
That dog...
went over the Rainbow Bridge.
(Candy welcomed him when he visited his mom's house in Jeju.)
- Candy. - You brat.
(It acted like it's savage, )
It was savage.
(but Candy was always by its owner's side.)
(Our youngest who was with us for 13 years)
The dog you mentioned...
- in your acceptance speech? - That's right.
(Our youngest who was with us for 13 years)
(He was worried about Candy during his acceptance speech...)
(on "2022 MBC Entertainment Awards.")
(The dog is quite old now.)
It died peacefully in my mom's arms.
I mentioned it during my acceptance speech,
but some people said it was a little overboard...
to mention it during an acceptance speech.
- No way. It was your family. - To me,
- it was like my family. - Of course.
To Mom, it must've meant much more.
With Candy around, she'd talk to it,
feed it, go for a walk, and everything.
She had a daily routine with it, so it was nice.
But with Candy gone,
she suffered from...
- pet loss syndrome. - It's not easy.
From what I saw, she seemed really down.
I can really relate as a fellow dog owner.
It terrifies me to even think about it.
- Imagining her dying like Candy. - Right.
- Kkotbun is already ten, so... - I'm worried about you too.
- Me too. - Right.
I can't see such sad videos...
because it already scares me.
My dog, Toto, also went over the Rainbow Bridge.
- I know. - Right.
I suffered a lot too.
- You too? - It was really hard.
It suddenly pops into my mind.
- That's right. - I go about my life,
but I'd suddenly think of it and tear up.
When my dog, Pookie, went over the Rainbow Bridge,
- it was really hard. - It's really hard.
After 4 to 5 months after Candy died,
she came to her senses.
She said it'd be better to have dogs,
so today, I went with her...
to see if we could adopt stray dogs.
Adopting dogs... But when I...
told her to adopt one quickly if it was too hard for her,
she said she felt bad for Candy.
My mom said the exact same thing.
She said it felt like she was replacing it with another dog...
like it's an object.
- That's right. - So she wasn't going to adopt one,
but she lives alone on Jeju Island.
When she wakes up, Candy isn't there,
so it's hard for her every morning.
That's right.
She feels lonely too. She has to eat alone.
- So... - She's reminded of it more.
We decided that it'd be better if she had a dog.
That's why we went to adopt a dog.
Candy was so adorable.
Any dog adopted by you would be lucky.
I treat dogs well. I treat them like a precious treasure.
I hope it comes to me like fate.
- I should raise it well. - Right.
She got a bit emotional.
What's with the weather?
It's cloudy today.
It didn't say it'd rain.
So do you eat carbs these days?
I eat whatever I want.
- Because you work out so much. - Work out?
(Staring outside the window for no reason)
There must be something outside the window.
My prayer has changed these days.
- "Please let my son marry well." - These days, guys my age...
Guys in their 40s work out hard.
People don't like it if we don't work out.
When I meet my friends these days, they would...
- It's "Show Me the Money." - talk about their sons-in-law,
- Here it is. Here's the beat. - their daughters-in-law...
That's the only thing they talk about. Their grandchildren...
They're all younger than you.
They're in their mid-30s.
They got married early.
They all have children.
Why would you talk about sons-in-law...
when we were talking about working out?
So when I...
talk with others,
I'd wonder, "Will my son even get married?"
I will. Don't worry.
- You should get married. - I should.
It's the exact same repertoire as my family's.
You gave a satisfying answer for your mom.
- Right. It's hard to say that too. - He does everything.
- Yes. - Is it there?
Please stop here, sir.
(They arrived somewhere before Mommynem starts again.)
It's here, Mom.
(I'll carry the bags.)
Gosh, you're carrying all the bags.
- It's heavy, right? - That's the least I could do.
- This one's heavy, right? - It's all right.
- We're good at carrying stuff. - Yes.
You'd be a jerk if you let your mom carry that.
It must be here. Why is it so well-managed?
(Impressed)
Hello.
- Hello. - Where is that?
- Hello. - Hello.
- Goodness, baby. - Do we have to put on slippers?
Goodness, baby. My gosh.
My goodness. There are pretty babies here.
Baby.
- Oh, gosh. - Baby.
Look at this guy.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
- Goodness. - How pretty.
A friend of mine from a community service...
introduced me to this place.
This is a pet grooming school.
The director of the place...
thought stray dogs needed to be groomed,
- Right. To be chosen. - so they can...
be adopted to a good place.
So she does that.
That's really important, though.
They need to be well-groomed...
- to be chosen. - That's right.
- That's right. - You said they needed...
pretty photos to be adopted well.
- That's right. - Right.
(A neat appearance is important for stray dog adoption.)
At the center where I do community service,
there are scruffy dogs.
After washing and grooming them,
- we'd take nice photos. - Right.
We posted the photos, and they got adopted abroad...
to the US, Germany and such.
- It can't be helped. - That's right.
- Of course. - Yes.
I was honestly surprised...
because the dogs there were well-groomed.
There are many adoption centers where dogs aren't well-groomed...
because there are just so many.
With a hope to find good owners,
they must've groomed them well.
- Gosh, that punk. - They'd groom and keep them neat.
My mom used to...
have two dogs.
One was Gongju,
and the other one was Candy. Those were the two.
Since then, she has volunteered...
at dog rescue centers from time to time.
Since my mom knows how rescue centers run,
we went to adopt dogs there.
Goodness. It likes people.
Gosh, baby.
- That one looks like Candy. - It looks exactly like Candy.
There, there.
- Hello. - See? Your mom likes it.
- She can't help but be drawn to it. - Come here.
- How cute. - There, there. Yes.
Come here.
- Come here. Baby. - It looks like Candy.
The one that looks exactly like Candy went to my mom.
How cute. Goodness.
There, there.
How sweet.
- It's like a baby. - Sweet baby.
These days,
- You're so sweet. - after COVID-19,
- There, there. - people travel a lot.
Where did that sweet thing come from?
This one was rescued...
after a pet store closed down.
It had a tumor...
in its tongue,
so we had it removed.
It hasn't been long since it had the surgery,
so it couldn't be adopted.
- Now, it's up for adoption. - Every dog has its story.
- There, there. - Its name is Nana.
- It's around nine months. - It's quite young.
- It's very young. - It's still a baby.
Look at the way it's looking at his mom.
- There, there. - Goodness.
Gosh, look at the dogs approaching him.
Mashi.
- How cute. - Are adoptions going well?
- Not really. No. - It's not going well?
Because the economy is bad,
there are way more people giving up their dogs.
There are fewer people willing to raise one.
- Goodness. - Yes.
- It's a difficult problem. - Not many can be adopted.
What do we do with all of them?
If there aren't any inquiries for adoption...
and if they stay here for too long,
I look for adopters abroad.
If the dogs are adopted abroad,
do the adopters pay for the plane tickets and everything?
- We pay for everything. - What?
- Yes. - Who pays for that?
- That's why people donate. - We do.
- I pay for it. - I see.
- That's where it's used. - You pay for it?
You pay for it?
- She does a good deed. - Yes.
Doesn't that mean you only spend money?
- You need to pay the rent too. - That's true, but...
Then you should make donations too.
- My goodness. - But I think...
it's a matter of where I focus on spending my money.
The money is ought to be spent anyway.
If I save money on one thing,
I can save these guys.
- I can save another life. - Exactly.
- So where I spend the money... - You can never do that...
if you don't love dogs.
- How cute. - You can never.
- You can never do it. - It's snuggling into my arms.
(His mom is deeply in love with the lovely dogs.)
- You like to kiss. - That one's cute too.
- So you like to kiss. - That guy is cute too.
(Filled with love)
My goodness.
How adorable.
There, there.
Baby.
(Kian84 is quietly lost in thought.)
Every time I see stray dogs,
I don't feel easy, to be really honest.
They're so pitiful. They can't even speak.
Yet, they like people.
They wag their tails at people because they like us.
- That's what's really sad. - The ones that approach me...
are also pitiful because they're so adorable.
But those that can't approach me are also pitiful.
Maybe they...
don't trust people. Or maybe...
With a timid character like that,
that dog would have a hard time meeting a new owner.
- It's just my thought, but... - I get how you feel.
Of course, I don't feel that good.
You care deeply about such things.
We went to eat together once,
and there was a fish in the fish tank.
He wanted to save the fish,
so he asked how much it was.
He wanted to buy it and release it in the river.
- It'd die right away. - If he releases it,
it get caught again.
I know I went overboard, but this happened too.
I went to have grilled clams on Jebu Island,
and I felt so bad for the clams.
I took them to a mudflat...
and buried them after digging the mud.
There are times when you feel that way.
That's right.
(He just feels bad for the dogs.)
- There, there. - Actually, their teeth...
need to be developed a lot.
(Passing through)
Their teeth fall out because they eat dog food.
This is so nice.
- That's right. - It approached him suddenly.
It came to my side.
(The cotton ball came to Kian84's side.)
It looks like Kkotbun.
(Fluffy like Kkotbun)
- You're so sweet. - It's snuggling into my arms.
(Patting)
Baby.
(Sniffing)
- Well, then... - How cute. That dog is really cute.
That guy is cute.
Is there a dog you're growing fond of?
That dog looks too much like Candy.
Look at that. It's sitting right next to him.
- Actually, I... - Yes?
- I've had two dogs. - Yes.
Thinking back, two dogs played with each other well.
- What? - It's like a baby. It's sleeping.
- What? - It's sleeping.
- It's their first encounter, and... - Yes.
It showed its belly. It's game over.
It has a great personality.
It's not easy for dogs to show their bellies,
unless they feel really comfortable.
I think this one is meant for us.
- It's lying next to me. - The one next to you?
This one is really shy around strangers.
- Really? - Yes.
This one realized it could survive with me.
Is that so?
Look at it. It's sitting right next to me.
- Is that so? - You're right. I was holding it.
It's so pretty.
I think you two have a similar disposition.
An INTP-type.
(When the rescuer was holding it earlier...)
It's only looking at you.
You're right. That punk.
(When it had a chance...)
- Oh, my. Goodness. - Oh, my.
It approached him first.
I guess it likes the smell of your body.
- It's sitting right next to you. - It's right here.
It wants me to take it.
The look in that dog's eyes...
My mom once had a dog...
- that was disowned four times. - Yes.
- Gongju. - It has the same look in the eyes.
- That one. - The other one?
The one on the bottom right.
Gongju was rescued from an illegal dog breeding facility.
- I see. - She was abused a lot.
We tried to put her in a cage,
she didn't want to go in.
Because she didn't have any good memory in a cage.
- Exactly. - She must've been really scared.
- It became a trauma. - Of course it did.
Goodness. So this baby is one year old.
- That one is 1 year old too? - That one is 1 year and a half.
- This one is nine months old. - Nine months? I see.
Goodness. Come home with me.
- How does it sleep like that? - Look at Nana sleeping.
- It's because it's still a baby. - Oh, my.
Babies sleep a lot.
Come with me.
You 2 can be friends. The 3 of us can live together.
The two of you, come with me. Okay?
- Hey, let's go to Jeju Island. - Okay?
Let's go to Jeju Island with me.
Ma'am, we don't just send our dogs for adoption.
There's this thing called foster period with adoption intent.
- Foster period? - During this period,
you should try living with them...
and see if you can protect them until they die.
Actually, these two had separate foster homes,
and they met each other here.
We also need to see if they can live well together.
After two weeks,
we'll decide if you can adopt them for sure.
The other dogs are really cute too.
I hope they meet nice owners soon too.
They're all registered under my name,
so for around three months, they'll be under my name,
but after three months, I'll transfer them to you for good.
If you don't have a foster period but adopt right away,
and if you can't handle it later,
- you have to give it up again. - It's different in real life.
- It'd be another scar for them. - So...
If they get ahead of themselves and adopt...
- They shouldn't be impulsive. - That'd scar the dogs more.
That's why you have a foster period.
If you're okay with raising the dogs...
after the two-week foster period, then the adoption is confirmed.
We should include the dogs on our national ID card.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Baby, are you sleepy? - That's what...
- we hope for. - Right?
- That way... - That way, they don't abandon dogs.
I'll raise them well.
Your mom's totally in love.
I'll film a video from time to time and send it to you.
- I can do that. - Right.
Then I'll bring the adoption application form.
- Please wait here. - Okay.
It's so properly managed.
They have a friendly personality too.
- Exactly. They play well. - They play well.
- They're close. - They must be best friends.
Right.
There were kids in middle school...
who were playful like this.
They'd get smacked when they cross the line.
They'd think, "Maybe I can beat this guy."
It's almost crossing the line.
It's so cute.
- That's fine, though. - Hey, stop it.
- This one is scared of people. - Hee Min, fill that form.
- That's right. - Come here.
Ma'am, I brought the adoption consent form.
Hee Min, you can see well, so fill it for me.
Since she's old...
The dogs are all active.
Please read carefully and fill the forms.
This one says you can't give up...
- your dogs to elsewhere. - So there are procedures.
- That's really good. - If something happens...
or a problem arises that you can't raise them,
you must return them to me.
- Return them? Okay. - Yes.
If you don't go through that, there could be a problem.
Before going there, I learned about it...
from a friend I made through a community service.
We talked a lot,
so the procedure went smoothly.
Next, a promise to provide fresh food to the dogs.
Next, both of them are white.
You're very loving, aren't you?
Ma'am, it's done.
- Okay. Thank you. - Sure.
- Right. - You're doing a good deed.
- You'll be blessed. - No. Not at all.
- I'll raise them well. - You'll be blessed.
(They have to leave now.)
There are many more. Right?
I keep...
- Don't show your scaredy-cat side. - I...
I keep worrying about the ones who couldn't be adopted.
(Sniffing)
Because you were worried about the other ones...
You'd want to take them all.
- Give each of them a hug. - A hug...
I'll take photos,
- at least. I've done it before. - Yes.
They need to get attention from social media,
so they have a higher chance to be adopted.
I'll take photos with all of them.
- Take one each. - Please take a photo with one each.
Kian84.
Smile.
(Proud)
That dog strangely looks like Ju Seung.
Ju Seung?
- It's better-looking than Ju Seung. - Ju Seung...
- It looks like Ju Seung. - It became a little stiff.
Look over here.
- Over here. - How sweet.
Is it still a baby?
- You need to find your owner. - It's still a baby.
Mashi.
(Pricking up its ears)
You're so cute.
This dog is...
Hee Min, you two look alike.
- May. - Smile.
- This one. - Yes, Joah is really pretty.
- You did a good thing. - Joah.
Many people would adopt them.
Ma'am, are we done...
- filling all the forms? - Yes, you did.
We'll make the final decision...
- two weeks later. - All right.
I'll prepare the cages...
- and other things for you. - Actually,
I didn't know what it'd be like,
so I brought these.
- They're quite heavy. - You're giving us a lot.
- What are they? - Goodness.
- They're dog treats. - Oh, dog treats.
It's not a lot.
(A bundle of dog treats she brought from Jeju Island)
I told my son to be their Santa for once.
Thank you.
To dogs, he's really like Santa.
- I know. - Yes.
Baby, come home with me.
- I can't change their names, right? - No, you can.
- I can change their names? - Yes.
Let's go.
- Let's go. - My sweetie.
- You found your owner. How cute. - Let's go.
- Thank you. - Not at all. Thank you.
Say goodbye. Let's go home.
- Say goodbye. - Bye, Taeyang.
- Say goodbye. - Say goodbye.
- Taeyang went through a lot. - Gosh, those poor kids.
I feel so bad.
- Oh, no. - Those guys...
- Their backs look so sad. - Thank you.
Baby.
(After going through the adoption process...)
- Mom, get in there. - Peekaboo.
- Get in, Mom. - Come with Mommy.
Baby, let's go home.
Hello.
Are you going to get on a flight?
They did the next day.
They said we could take only one dog per person.
- I see. - I see.
You can't take two?
- So my mom's friend came. - Let's go.
Let's go home with Mommy.
Mom, put on your seat belt.
(They set off to Kian84's house after putting their seat belts on.)
- It's cute, right? - It's confused.
That's when it started to get a little scared.
"Where are they taking me?"
There, there. Peekaboo.
- Peekaboo. - She treats it like a baby.
Goodness. It's cute.
Dalkong. Dalkong?
I'll buy you toys.
How will you name them?
Alkong and Dalkong.
(Alkong and Dalkong)
Your mom named them...
- Alkong and Dalkong. - She had named them already.
- Alkong and Dalkong. - She named them well.
Alkong and Dalkong.
Alkong.
So that they'll live with me in a lovey-dovey manner,
I named them Alkong and Dalkong.
I personally think the names my mom comes up with are a bit old.
- Why? They're so nice. - Candy, Gongju,
Alkong, and Dalkong are a bit too...
(Sucking in a breath)
Had it been me, I would've named a male dog...
- Gaedol... - It's one-dimensional.
And a female dog Gaesun.
Those names are worse.
A dog wouldn't want to be called Gaesun.
They're homely names.
- Let's do that later. - Here.
(Sticking out)
Do you want to look outside the window?
- Look outside the window. - Let it look outside the window.
Let it get a good look of the world.
Did you drink coffee? Do you want a sip of coffee?
- I had coffee. - Did you have coffee?
It's your first time seeing Gimpo?
This one...
plays well even when there are other dogs.
- That one is more docile. - Yes.
This one is more like a princess.
Yes.
How long has it been since Candy passed away?
It passed away on August 2.
- It has been over four months. - You went through a lot, Mom.
I had a dream.
- I told you about it. - Yes.
A yellow crane flew in the sky.
- Okay. - Then blue cranes flew in the sky.
- In your dream? - So...
That's right. I had this dream on the day of the 49th-day ritual.
I feel a bit strange whenever I talk about this.
She had the 49th-day ritual for the dog.
- Really? - Yes.
My mom did it personally.
- It's the Buddhist style. - Being a Buddhist,
she held the 49th-day ritual.
- Candy was part of the family. - Yes.
It made me think, "Candy went to a good place."
- That's right. - It made me feel relieved.
Next year... I mean, in its next life,
it'll be reborn as a person.
- It'll be reborn as a pretty woman. - Yes.
It'll be reborn as a pretty woman from a rich family.
That sounds nice.
(As they hope that Candy has gone to a good place, )
(the sky turns dark.)
Thank you.
Thank you. All right.
- Hold on. - Let's hurry up and go.
Get out slowly.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
- Now... - Let's lay it first.
- Let's lay the pad first. - Let's do it so that they can pee.
- Hey. - Dalkong, come on out.
- All right. - I'll lay the pad.
Come here.
Let's lay the pad.
- Come here. - It's confused.
It's confused. "Where am I?"
The dogs are confused.
Of course, they are.
This one is definitely more shy.
- Come here. - Come here.
Gosh, it's shy.
It's okay.
(Laughing)
(Frozen)
Why are you so scared?
It's okay.
(I'm telling you that it's okay.)
Come here.
It's walking around the house.
Leave it be so that it can get used to the house.
Alkong is walking around so energetically.
Do dogs adjust quickly...
when you bring them home?
- Does it depend on the dog? - Yes.
- Look. - It depends on the dog.
One adjusted easily,
but the other one...
- Did it freeze? - The dog that has been abused...
- was very wary. - That's right.
It gets scared easily.
Which bowls should I use for water?
(Grabbing)
(Why do the two bowls look familiar?)
(They're the rice bowls Kian84 has used for every meal.)
- Are they the same bowls? - Yes.
(He used them even when his mom came over.)
Come here.
You use the same dishware for people and dogs.
That's right. I'm the same.
Come here. Let's drink water.
- Here. - Drink water.
Let's drink water.
There you go.
(Drinking water from Mom)
It drinks water well.
Look at its butt.
Dogs that are very shy...
don't drink water in a nervous state.
You're right.
Joy, you have so much information about dogs.
- She knows everything. - I love dogs so much.
(Hold on a second.)
You're a host of "Animal Farm."
- I've been one for five years. - Didn't you know?
That must be why you're so knowledgeable.
Joy also hosted an agility show with me on MBC.
Yes.
- In the eyes of an expert, - Okay.
Are the dogs feeling okay?
Yes, they're doing better than I expected.
Are they okay?
Some dogs...
can't live with other dogs due to trauma.
- They can't live with other dogs. - Some dogs...
can't open up to people.
I heard that...
it could be bad to raise multiple dogs in the same house.
- Yes. - Really?
You call them one-man dogs.
Those dogs only bond...
with one owner.
It's better to avoid getting any other dogs in that case.
- Haetnim is like that. - Really?
Kkotbun is the same.
(Kkotbun is the same.)
(I don't want anyone except for Sung Hwan!)
It isn't always a good idea to keep them with another dog.
That's right.
Let me go to a mart.
(He puts his jacket back on.)
Mom had just gotten off the airplane.
I hadn't eaten either, so I decided to go grocery shopping.
- "Big brother, go and buy food." - So...
- you don't need leashes? - No, don't buy leashes.
- Don't buy leashes. - Okay.
Buy dog food...
and ceramic bowls.
Ceramic bowls are the best. I use a ceramic bowl too.
"Big brother, go and buy tasty food."
- My goodness. - It's so cute.
My goodness.
(He's on his way to run an errand for his mom.)
It keeps raining instead of snowing.
I bet being with your mom...
reminds you...
of the way you ran errands in your childhood.
- My steps were different back then. - Really?
(Happy)
- I was excited. - How cute!
- You got a reward back then... - Yes.
- for an errand. - That's right.
You got a reward for buying tofu.
You got a reward.
I wanted to try on my mom's heels.
So I went on an errand...
with the condition of wearing my mom's heels.
Really?
- I wore high heels. - Idols sure are different.
(Idols sure are different.)
(She was bound to be big.)
(He arrives at the supermarket with calm steps.)
(I'm hungry, so let's hurry up and buy the needed items.)
(He takes a shopping basket as he walks.)
What I need...
(Let's see.)
(Cabbage, come on.)
- Cabbage. - He didn't even look.
He didn't even look.
I don't like to study the produce for a long time.
I don't do that either.
(He adds garlic to the basket.)
(He picks the bag of onions that's at the top.)
(He keeps shopping without making a single mistake.)
He'll be done in less than ten minutes.
I know.
This one.
Fish sauce.
(He picks this and that.)
He's so fast.
- It's here. - Thank you.
- Seaweed. - Seaweed.
- He'll make seaweed soup. - It was my mom's birthday present.
- You'll make seaweed soup. - Seaweed soup.
(Looking around)
The dog supplies...
(He remembers the items he needs to get...)
(after filling the basket with groceries.)
They're here.
Dog chew.
You pick the dog food...
- with more care. - Seriously.
(I'll get this one.)
I'll get a small one.
You don't know their tastes yet,
so it must be hard to get food for them.
This one.
Why are there so many types of dog food?
(Which one is better?)
The dog food prices...
(The prices differ a lot.)
The dog food prices differ a lot.
Since it's their first day, they should eat something tasty.
- It's their first day. - He picked the most expensive one.
The dog food prices varied widely.
Dog food.
Dog chew.
Dog bowl.
(I almost forgot!)
(Where is it? Come on out.)
I'll look for it just once. If I can't find it...
Your mom told you to buy a ceramic bowl.
- That's right. - I couldn't find them.
Forget it.
(I guess they don't sell them.)
(He gives up on the dog bowl and goes to pay.)
They can use your rice bowls...
- for a day. - Exactly.
(He heads home after paying.)
Have a nice day.
Mom must be hungry.
(Meanwhile, Kian84's mom is at home with Alkong and Dalkong.)
(Hopping)
You're happy.
- You're happy. My goodness. - My goodness.
Oh, my.
That one has adjusted fully.
(It's comfortable now.)
Do you want it? It's Kian84's.
(Biting)
(Alkong takes Kian84's plushie.)
Here.
(She pats Dalkong as well.)
That one is still shy.
Maltese dogs...
tend to value their own territories...
- and time. - Really?
- They're like cats in that sense. - Really?
The Pomeranian, Alkong.
It pants. It breathes very quickly.
Apparently, Pomeranians are prone to heart issues.
That's right.
Is that why Pomeranians stick out their tongues?
- When people developed the breed, - That's right.
They preferred the dogs with a shorter muzzle...
and kept making such dogs.
- They have a short muzzle. - Yes.
Thus, many Pomeranians...
- have breathing issues. - They have short breaths,
oversized hearts, and bad knees.
That's right. They have bad knees.
Malteses and Pomeranians...
- must have their knees checked out. - No matter what.
Is it a must?
- Breeding led to those problems. - In most cases, yes.
Everyone is an expert.
Dalkong.
(Alkong and Dalkong, let's live a healthy and long life.)
My goodness.
(They have a happy time.)
(The real son comes back from running an errand.)
This dog is something else.
It's so energetic...
that it doesn't stay still for a second.
- Really? - This dog is something else.
(Kian84's mom's eyes are fixed on the fur babies.)
- Where are their snacks? - Here.
Give me some dog food.
I'll lure them with dog food.
- Give me their snacks. - How cute!
Gosh, look at that punk.
Let's eat. Come here.
All right.
Alkong, come here. Dalkong, come here.
(Alkong gets close upon hearing about the snacks.)
- Alkong. - Alkong sticks to her.
- Sit. - It sticks to her.
Dalkong, come here.
Both of them are coming.
All right. Dalkong.
(A bite for Dalkong)
You eat with gusto.
Wait.
(Alkong gets a bite as well.)
Dalkong, there you go.
I'll give you some food.
Let's eat some food.
(Meanwhile, the other baby...)
(is cooking diligently for people.)
Where are their bowls?
They didn't have dog bowls.
- Didn't they have dog bowls? - No.
- Didn't they have dog bowls? - Mom, just use those bowls today.
They're for water.
- Which bowls don't you use? - Just use plastic bowls.
- But... - I eat rice in those bowls.
- Give me bowls you don't use. - What?
- Give me bowls you don't use. - Just use plastic bowls.
(He gives her a plastic container.)
Shall I use this?
It's too big.
My goodness.
You don't eat rice in this, right?
I eat rice in it.
Do you eat rice in it?
(Dejected)
(Then which bowls should I use for my fur babies?)
He's cooking seaweed soup diligently.
You should eat dog food.
- I should eat dog food with them. - I know.
Then your mom think, "I shouldn't have done that."
He'll get scolded for stealing Alkong's food.
(That might happen.)
(She looks for bowls Alkong and Dalkong can use.)
(In the end, she takes her son's sauce bowls.)
Come here. Let's eat.
Come here. I'll give you food.
When you come to my place, I'll give you food in proper bowls.
Let's see. Come here.
Come here.
This is yours. Here.
Eat.
(In the end, Alkong and Dalkong take the sauce bowls.)
(The son keeps cooking after giving away the sauce bowls.)
(He rinses rice with care.)
I haven't seen you cook in a long while.
(He covers it with a towel.)
(He applies pressure with a dumbbell.)
- He's cooking rice in a pot. - Rice in a pot.
(He attempts to cook rice in a pot for his mom!)
You need to control the fire well.
I cook my meals at home these days. It boosts my self-esteem.
- It does, right? - Really?
It keeps you healthier than ordering deliveries, right?
When you order deliveries,
the plastic containers stress you out.
- That's right. - I agree with that.
- Let's say I make seaweed soup. - Okay.
I add leftover kimchi to the leftover seaweed soup...
- for another meal. - To the seaweed soup?
What?
(What do you add...)
(to the seaweed soup?)
I eat the seaweed and kimchi soup for another meal...
- and have some leftovers. - Okay.
Then I stir-fry rice with it.
- Not even dogs will eat that. - My goodness.
- Hey, not even dogs will eat that. - Listen.
- Is it tasty? - Unless I stop eating it,
it'll go on forever.
You'll use it like the perpetual broth.
- It'll keep getting a new life. - The perpetual broth!
It'll go on.
No other chefs can copy him.
(Emptying)
(He soaks seaweed, the key ingredient.)
He cooks with ease.
Did you add olive oil?
I was going to add sesame oil.
You bought sesame oil earlier.
- Didn't you have it? - I forgot.
- Olive oil is healthy. - That's right.
(He adds meat to the healthy olive oil.)
- Is that duck? - It's pork.
What? Who adds pork to seaweed soup?
Not beef?
- I think outside the box. - Right.
(He seeks freedom by thinking outside the box.)
He thinks outside the box when he cooks.
(He flaunts his cooking philosophy.)
That's right. It should've been sesame oil.
I added olive oil by mistake.
(Although it's belated, he adds some sesame oil.)
(He stir-fries meat diligently.)
(Serious)
(He hasn't shown such refreshing skills...)
(since making his perpetual fried rice.)
It's like "Culinary Class Wars."
I don't know if I told you this.
My dad wanted to send me off...
to a culinary high school.
It was his plan to open a restaurant for me...
after retiring as a civil servant.
That was his thought behind his desire to send me there.
Who knows what would've happened had I attended that school?
I might've starred in "Culinary Class Wars."
No.
(However, he became a dark cook.)
A dark cook?
(He's a cooking monster who stir-fries all ingredients.)
I think it's the same as drawing.
It's the act of creating new things.
His nickname is Stir-Fry Monster.
(He adds oysters that are in season to the pot.)
- I planned to use Manila clams. - Right.
- But they weren't in season. - No.
So I used oysters instead.
(He adds garlic as well.)
(Stir-frying)
(He adds soaked seaweed as well.)
(Without checking the doneness, he adds water and boils.)
I don't like to follow the rules.
- That's right. It isn't fun. - I don't like instructions.
I don't like getting bound by a specific style of art.
It isn't that hard.
When I cook, I always know that it'll be tasty.
Also, I usually don't taste the dish I'm cooking.
But I tasted the dish today too.
My goodness.
(The confident Stir-Fry Monster tasted the dish...)
(for Yoon Kyung Mi, the judge.)
It's in my hand.
Is she a judge?
(For the veteran judge, he controls the saltiness carefully.)
(Tasting)
It's nice.
The name of the dish is...
Pig That Married Oyster.
- I came up with the name. - Pig That Married Oyster.
Let me tell you what the name reminds you of.
When you go to your grandparents' place,
some restaurants have an ambitious name...
on a faded signboard.
- You know what I mean, right? - But...
- The closed restaurants. - Yes.
- It's a cute name. - I'm so curious...
about the taste.
This seaweed soup contains oysters...
and pork.
I don't think they wanted that.
It's nice.
(It's a pretty nice wedding.)
Pig That Married Oyster.
(Pig That Married Oyster)
I just need to wait for the rice.
Shall I take out some kimchi I made this year?
This is the kimchi I made this year. This is the fresh kimchi.
- It's really tasty. - Put some there.
(Opening)
(She brought kimchi from Jeju Island and filled Kian84's fridge.)
(Mom's precious kimchi)
That's all you need.
(That's all you need for a tasty meal.)
Gosh, that's..
Green onion kimchi.
I'd make ramyeon right away.
Let's eat this.
(Grabbing)
- Mom. - Yes?
You must be tired from being on the plane all day.
(A small present for his tired mom)
(He gives one to his mom first.)
Well done.
It's tasty.
I need to take it to restore my stamina.
(After using a short break to restore his stamina, )
(he moves Pig That Married Oyster to the table.)
I'll put it here.
(He forgoes a trivet for the presentation.)
- We might not have enough rice. - What?
- We might not have enough rice. - That's a lot.
Didn't you burn the rice?
The bottom was a bit burnt,
- but it was fine otherwise. - You're good.
I was worried, but you did much better than I expected.
(Opening)
(He transfers meat to the pan using hands.)
She said she wouldn't eat meat, but I felt like I should cook some.
That's right. You need your protein.
(Stir-Fry Monster pan-fries meat with his burning filial love.)
You really look like a chef.
Moms don't eat meat unless their sons ask for it.
That's right. I pan-fried meat on purpose.
Well done.
Take a seat.
Gosh, there are many side dishes.
Oh, my.
(With love, Stir-Fry Monster made a birthday meal for his mom.)
(Meat has been pan-fried nicely.)
(Rice cooked in a pot is fluffy.)
(There's Mom's kimchi from Jeju Island.)
(Then there's me, Pig That Married Oyster!)
It's like the wedding between an oyster and a pig.
Let's eat. Oh, my.
- Happy birthday, Mom. - Thank you.
(Enjoy the food.)
Try the kimchi.
- Did you make it? - Yes.
(She finally tastes Stir-Fry Monster's masterpiece.)
I'm curious to see how she will react to it.
(How is it?)
(How does the seaweed soup taste?)
You did well to make the seaweed soup.
- Is it okay? - Really?
Was she really hungry?
(The Stir-Fry Monster quickly tries a bite as well.)
What?
- It's good. - Right. It's good.
You did well.
Oysters and pork must go well together.
- They worked well together. - Wasn't the oyster fishy?
The oyster's refreshing...
and strong taste...
was balanced with the pork's clean taste.
So they both ate each other.
- The two were meant to be. - Right.
- I cook well. - Right.
(The birthday meal he made for his mother is a success.)
(It's been a while for them to have a nice meal together.)
The seaweed soup is good.
(She enjoys her son's seaweed soup.)
She's really enjoying it.
It must be good.
It was her first meal that day.
It tastes even better because my son made it.
The seaweed soup would taste good with the green onion kimchi.
Gosh, it's the best.
Add some water when you heat it up again.
- Right. - Right.
It will become salty.
- It's a bit salty. - Right.
- What? - It's salty.
I didn't know if it was salty when it was hot.
I could taste it accurately once it cooled down.
That is why I eat food quickly.
- I see. - I see.
(So that was why you ate quickly.)
It's very salty.
- Just add some water. - I should add some water.
Right.
She's eating it as she's happy that her son made it for her.
This is beef, right? This isn't pork, right?
It's pork!
It's pork.
- Oh, this is pork? - Yes.
(Humming)
But how does it taste like this with pork?
Oh, I see. You put in oysters.
- It has everything healthy. - Right.
Everyone needs to think outside the box.
(The dish of the Dark Spoon who thought out of the box)
(She scrapes the rice and puts it into the seaweed soup.)
- Is that enough? - This is enough.
You eat a lot less now.
It's like that when you get old.
It's harder to digest food.
My mom said the same thing.
Is it hard for you to digest the food?
(Worried)
The rice hasn't been fully cooked.
What? Really?
It hasn't been fully cooked?
Can't you tell? It hasn't been fully cooked.
It tastes fine. What do you mean?
It hasn't been fully cooked.
Stir-Fry Monster has been eliminated.
- It's good. - That's not what I'm talking about.
How can you tell me it hasn't been fully cooked after finishing it all?
- Is that sungnyung? - I decided to make sungnyung.
(Rummaging)
I wasn't able to prepare an envelope, Mom.
What?
This is your birthday gift.
Gosh!
Are you a loan shark?
- Why not get the gold bills? - Right. You could've done that.
It's a better feeling like that as it's nice and thick.
Why didn't you divide it to smaller bills then?
Those bills were my only choice.
It looks like he emptied up an ATM.
(Fortunately, he got out the money normally...)
(from the ATM in the supermarket.)
(He got out a thick bundle of bills.)
I know what you're saying.
- It feels better with more bills. - As it seems like more money.
Happy birthday.
(A big birthday gift)
It was 1,000 dollars.
You still should've found something to put it into.
- There's her genuine smile. - You're giving me...
cash like that.
- Thank you! - Here you are.
This is better than the golden bills.
Right.
This is a lot of money.
Giving money like this helps you spend wisely.
Right. I should spend wisely. It's from my son.
(After a big money gift...)
Here.
The sungnyung must be good.
(They go for another round with the warm sungnyung.)
(Slurping)
- This is great. Try it. - Is it okay?
- It's really good. - I like regular rice.
(You can have all of it, Mom.)
(Eating)
Have it with the green onion kimchi.
Gosh, it's so salty.
Was it that salty?
It became much saltier after it cooled down.
- I still finished a bowl. - What?
I ate it as you made it for me.
- I ate it when I was hungry. - Right.
I can taste it accurately now that I'm full.
It's hard for something to be bad as your first meal.
He keeps adding water.
It's a new start of the perpetual broth.
(His mom rinses out the saltiness with the sungnyung.)
It must've been really salty for her.
Gosh.
(Looking intently)
What are the dogs doing?
- Gosh. - How adorable.
- They're adapting well. - This is what I think.
It's much better to see them inside the house.
- Of course. - Much better.
- Go out for walks often. - It's a must.
They need to be out often.
It would be great for you to exercise as well.
- Right. - Jeju Island will be great.
Did you put in more water?
- That will solve things. - I put in a lot.
Gosh, I was still served with seaweed soup on my birthday.
It finally tastes right.
For my next birthday,
it would be great to eat with my daughter-in-law.
Gosh! The conversation always ends with marriage.
Okay.
- It has begun. - Next year?
I heard you will have some luck to get married next year.
- That was what I was told. - Right.
I felt so jealous to see Jang Woo.
- Jang Woo? - Right.
I'll make sure to get married before you turn 70.
I think my mother's heart has become a lot warmer.
It felt great to bring over the dogs that were ownerless.
What's greater for me is that my mother felt really happy.
That was what brought me joy.
Alkong and Dalkong.
I think you two have found a great owner.
Let's have a great life together.
Mom!
Continue to be who you are.
Nice.
My son made me seaweed soup.
You left all of the soup as it was salty.
No. I had a lot of it.
The seawater.
- I can have more. - No!
Don't force yourself!
It's still the same.
It was salty earlier.
- It was good though. - Right.
(Let's Be Happy with Alkong and Dalkong)
(I Live Alone)
I've waited for this day.
Well,
I've really been waiting for this moment.
- I wondered when you would come. - Oh, thank you.
I made my hot debut as an officiant,
and the one who scoffed at me the most is here.
I watched that episode and you said a lot of things.
- Oh, right. I'm sorry. - Everything was revealed.
I couldn't help myself.
(Hyun Moo was the officiant at Jang Woo's wedding.)
(My, as for me, I...)
(He's talking about himself so much.)
(He couldn't stop his mouth out of excitement.)
(Ju Seung, you little punk!)
I went ahead of myself.
Right.
"Adrenaline."
It's Christmas!
Gosh, it's cold!
(Ju Seung has come out in his martial arts uniform.)
You're in that uniform again!
It's really comfortable.
(He enjoys winter with his favorite uniform.)
(He starts running somewhere.)
Hello.
(Hi!)
(He keeps moving after saying hello to the elder in town.)
- He's doing a Fun Run. - Right.
He's influenced by me.
He was a slow-jogging member with you.
Right. I influenced him a lot.
(Just like his muse, Hyun Moo, )
(he's doing a slow Fun Run.)
Gosh, this is great.
(Ju Seung starts slowing down.)
A lot of my seniors are here today.
(The place he has come to early in the morning)
It's a place I visit often that's very closeby.
This is the mountain gym in my area.
The sunlight and my seniors.
My seniors are exercising there.
Even though they are fairly old,
I see them do their best to work out their muscles.
That helps me freshen up my mind.
We had the Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day recently.
I got quite shocked that day.
I realized that I was out of shape.
(The sprint during the Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day)
He was awful.
It was because you didn't make the face of a monkey.
Doing that makes you run faster.
Ji Hyeon was so fast.
(He finished last as he didn't make the face of a monkey.)
This was shocking. He lost to Jang Woo.
(Do you know why Ju Seung can't run well?)
(I don't know why he runs like a duck.)
(He was ridiculed in front of everyone.)
That was why I decided to reset my heart...
and get back into shape.
I've been working out outside in the winter.
(He started working out outside in the winter.)
(That was why Ju Seung came out early in the morning.)
(Martial Artist Ju Seung's pride was hurt.)
- That was a long time ago. - A lot of time has passed.
- He's good. - That was four years ago.
(I will try to recover my reputation.)
To have the same heart, I dressed up in the same outfit.
- I see. - Right.
(He starts with a simple warmup.)
(Okay. Let's go.)
(He starts crawling on the floor.)
- That looks tough to do. - That's tough to do.
- It's a full-body workout. - It's a workout we haven't seen.
Three.
(What kind of workout are you doing?)
Go.
It's a workout that develops the muscles and flexibility.
It's the Spider-Man pushup.
Spider-Man climbs walls.
This is done on the ground instead.
Like this and this.
(Fully focused)
A lot of people do that abroad.
It works as a stretch and pushup at the same time.
(He gets on the floor as if he was climbing a wall.)
(It's as if his hands stick to the ground.)
(It looks like he was climbing a wall when turned around.)
- Gosh. - I'm climbing a wall.
That's really hard to do.
Twenty.
(That's a fascinating young man.)
(He tidies up his pants next.)
Let's go!
- He's cheering himself up. - Who are you saying that to?
(It's time to wake up now, Martial Artist Ju Seung.)
(He does a straight handstand.)
(He even does pushups on top of that.)
- There you go. - That's surprising.
- Not everyone can do that. - While doing a handstand?
That's insane.
When cold air comes through,
it makes me realize I'm alive.
When we take cold showers,
there's a rush of adrenaline.
- It's just like that. - My gosh!
Why do they keep playing videos of wild animals?
And it's always so sudden.
One, two, three, four.
(He easily pulls off the advanced workout.)
That's really hard to do.
(Letting out a shout)
(His face starts getting crumpled up even more.)
He must've used all his strength with the handstand.
(Groaning)
(Flapping)
What's that?
(He ends up stopping during his flap.)
(Should I try this instead?)
I was inspired by Hyun Moo.
I must inspire you a lot.
He copies every single move I do.
He's a follower of yours.
Gosh.
(Panting)
(He does it until the end even as he cries out.)
Twenty-three!
Right.
(Mumbling)
(He does his best to recover his reputation as a martial artist.)
That must've been a big shock to you.
Twenty-four. Let's do one more.
- One more. - One more.
- One more. - He's going to do 25.
(Screaming)
Twenty-five.
(That's enough.)
(Groaning)
(Panting)
(He plops down to the ground.)
(Feeling dizzy)
(Only the sound of panting can be heard from him.)
Gosh.
As I spent 2025,
I continued to do 25 of them.
(Responding)
If I do 26 next year,
I'll be increasing the numbers by one each year.
(Impressed)
It will feel like an upgrade.
- He didn't say anything amazing. - That's great.
- That's great. - I love their response.
- So... - You'll be doing 26!
(Bright)
It looks a lot more refreshing than being in a gym.
Gosh, that was great.
(Shall I go back home now?)
(Ju Seung warms up his legs.)
- It's been a while. - It's his shukuchi!
- Shukuchi! - You still do that?
(He excitedly sets off with his shukuchi.)
But doing that does make him look fast.
Right.
Gosh, that's great!
He looks excited as well.
I was even faster with my running shoes.
(Retching)
Did I overdo myself?
(Letting out a sigh)
(Let's just walk normally.)
But a little bit of that made me feel warm.
(Ju Seung returns home.)
Gosh, it's cold. That was tough.
Let's see.
I must eat.
(He fills the pot with water first.)
(He starts humming at the thought of eating.)
Should I use this?
All right.
What is that rectangular pan? Did you buy that?
I received an award at a movie awards ceremony.
- That was given as a prize. - Right!
- Gosh! - Ju Seung won an award!
Where did you get an award?
At the Seoul Global Movie Awards,
I received the Entertainer Award.
- Really? - Right.
(Entertainer Award)
(Lee Ju Seung)
("Lee Ju Seung Wins Entertainer Award at SGMA")
("Lee Ju Seung of I Live Alone Wins Award Alone")
It was a movie awards ceremony...
and you received the Entertainer Award?
They had that award.
It's an award given to those...
who are entertainers amongst movie actors.
Ju Seung sometimes...
goes to film festivals as a judge.
Pay attention to his social media.
- He posts everything. - I do see his posts.
I just don't press like.
- You canceled your like. - Gosh.
He was being all showy on his post.
(The nice friend actually pressed like on his post.)
(Checking the temperature)
I just did a workout and it was winter.
I needed some fat and protein.
That was why I prepared some pork belly...
and to help me warm up,
I got the spicy stir-fried ramyeon.
I'm planning to have those two together.
Should I make some gochujang?
(Should I make some gochujang?)
(Getting a generous amount)
When it comes to pork belly,
there are people who have ssamjang or gochujang with it.
But I prefer gochujang.
- Same here! - Same here!
- Gochujang? - I prefer gochujang as well.
- Gochujang tastes better for me. - Right.
Ssamjang tastes a bit weak.
As for me, I go for 1.5 portions of gochujang,
(Gochujang 1.5)
one portion of sesame oil,
and one portion of sugar.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Startled)
Gosh, what do I do?
- Since it was winter. - Winter?
I thought you were in a snow fight.
It was a snow performance.
All right.
(The winter food expert starts cooking again.)
(He gets a strip of pork belly...)
(and puts it on top of the heated pan.)
(Focused)
(One more strip!)
(One must have three strips.)
(He even prepares the ramyeon while cooking the pork belly.)
(He starts humming as things go smoothly.)
(Sizzling)
This is it!
(He even puts in some kimchi.)
Nice!
(I'm a stir-fried ramyeon chef today.)
(He even plates it nicely.)
Ju Seung cooks well.
(The meal gets prepared as he hums.)
(He picks up the cheese powder.)
(Tapping)
- Since it was winter. - You have it really high up.
You must really like that.
I like the feeling of snow.
(That's enough.)
Okay.
(Winter has come to the bowl of stir-fried ramyeon.)
(Pork belly is always exciting to see.)
(There's even his secret gochujang.)
(Ju Seung's feast is ready.)
I should send a picture to Mom.
(I must take a picture of this.)
The flash went off.
The food looks bad when the flash goes off.
- It looked like a crime scene. - Right?
Thank you for the food.
(Let's start eating.)
(He puts the stir-fried ramyeon on top of the pork belly...)
(and makes a big wrap.)
(Satisfied)
(Crunchy)
Gosh, that's spicy.
It was too spicy.
It was even spicier with the spicy stir-fried ramyeon.
(With the spicy stir-fried ramyeon and the spicy chili pepper, )
Gosh, it's hot.
(his mouth starts to burn.)
(Sucking in air)
(Groaning)
He looks like he's about to cry.
He looks like the dog he dressed up.
(His eyes look just like Coco's.)
His eyes look just like Coco's.
(I can't stop having something good even though it's spicy.)
You seem to eat food as if it was some kind of challenge.
(He goes head-to-head with the spicy food.)
He's going to the restroom for sure.
(Emptying the plate clean)
He ate everything.
Gosh, it's making me drool.
Gosh, that was good.
(Clapping)
I feel too lazy to wash the dishes. Shall I do them later?
(He pushes back doing the dishes to another time.)
It's going to be cold.
(Let's head out.)
(He heads somewhere while humming winter songs.)
(The place he heads to excitedly...)
(is near Yangjae?)
I'm here.
(Ju Seung arrives somewhere.)
All right.
(Heave-ho!)
(Both of his hands are full with his bags.)
- He has a bag and a big backpack. - Did he pack a lunchbox?
Hello.
Where is this?
(A place where colorful boxes welcome you)
It's a toy store!
I've been coming here often for my hobby.
It's a model car store.
I see RC cars too.
My gosh. I really wanted to buy toy cars from that brand.
- There are almost every car model. - Exactly.
At the store, you can also buy products...
to tune and paint the model cars.
Here's how I ended up getting into model cars.
The development of AI has been progressing rapidly lately.
Our world is going digital quickly.
So I wanted to go the other way...
and looked for old-school hobbies.
That explains my interest in dinosaurs.
- I want to go back to the old days. - The old days.
I know what you mean by this.
I've been getting into watches these days.
I'm not talking about the automatic ones.
- I'm into mechanical ones... - Okay.
- because they're not run by AI. - I see.
To get that repaired,
watchmakers would have to work on it...
for over six months like the old days.
I really like that.
Technology has crept far into our daily lives.
- I just... - You have many machines at home.
- You have so many of them at home. - Listen.
(Moomoo's house is filled with machines.)
I'm into the human touch and old-school hobbies too.
I didn't know you were too.
Didn't you interrupt him,
- so you could steal this idea? - Right.
(That's right.)
I'm setting it up.
- "Old-school hobbies are mine." - Yes.
Old-School Moo.
Old-School Moo?
So I thought of model cars.
I've been hooked on this hobby for two months now.
Model cars were first manufactured...
a long time ago around 1968.
Some cartoons like "Dash! Yonkuro" were...
popular in Korea.
And especially "Bakuso Kyodai Lets and Go" was...
a huge hit in Korea.
I really liked this cartoon.
- It was a huge hit. - I liked this one.
Guys around my age or slightly older guys...
probably played with model cars.
There can't be a single one who didn't.
Everyone bought model cars...
and played with them at school back in the day.
(Dad?)
It's Choi Min Sik.
(I'm playing with the toy car.)
(Back then, in front of the stationery stores...)
- Right. There were tracks. - I remember that.
The stores with 360° tracks...
- were popular. - The 360° tracks. Right.
- I can smell the childhood vibe... - Right?
- from the video. - People miss that,
so they go back to model cars.
That's right. Oh, how I miss the good old days.
In the end, this world is a cycle.
People will come back to the old-school hobbies.
(The old-school guy's journey of hobbies)
And nunchucks are retro too.
- Right. - You like anything retro.
You can see me here and there on his journey.
It's the head.
(He studied dinosaurs to go back to the origin.)
(He now has a model car hobby, the ideal hobby of the old days.)
So we've been following the life of one man, right?
(Laughing)
What's consistent with your hobbies is that...
- your hobbies are classic. - Right.
He's consistent with his hobbies.
Wait.
(Whizzing)
- Hello. - Hello.
Sir.
- Wait, the lap time. - You're already here.
(A model car is racing super fast along the track.)
- That's super fast. - That's crazy.
Gosh, it's so fast.
I broke the record again.
What? My gosh.
It's 18.4 seconds.
- My gosh. What? Eighteen seconds? - This...
It's 18.49 seconds.
Actually, anyone with a hint of interest in model cars knows him.
- Really? - Really?
He's also a model car painter.
- He's such a good painter. - Gosh.
His skills are on another level.
I also wanted to paint my own model car.
So I could have a car of my own.
- Oh, my. - I'm here to paint my car.
Once you customize the paint job, it becomes a one-of-a-kind car.
- Right. - Yes.
I'd get more attached to my car, and at competitions,
I can easily spot my car.
Let me hurry.
(He unpacks a mysterious box.)
I got this box from my legendary senior.
He used this box when he first got into model cars.
I have products for the paint job.
I can store three model cars.
He remodeled the box before giving it to me.
It's like a tool box.
I've been turning the motor whenever I had time.
I kept turning it on my way here.
- You did? - I did.
- You have to do that? - I need to break in the motor.
Let's say the motor is good for 80 years.
Then the car is the fastest at 79 years.
- It gets faster the more it's used? - Yes.
- The best scenario is... - Really?
That you use it for the competition...
- and it goes off right after. - And it's gone.
Right before it goes off.
- So you can beat me? - Of course.
I want to paint it green for the Christmas vibe.
I want to add red dots too.
- I want it to look like a tree. - I see. With red?
I'm curious.
I think I need to buy red and silver spray paint.
- First... - Good job.
Doing this toward the end of the year must be exciting.
Okay.
Then the silver spray...
(The colorful spray paint...)
(fills up the displays.)
My gosh. This is...
Wouldn't it cost a lot of money to buy the colors you want?
My gosh. Totally.
- Is there a pearly one? Yes. - You want glitters, right?
- It needs to glitter. - Let's see.
This one. You can pick 1 among these 3.
The colors come in different shades.
They're all silver, but one can be aluminium silver.
There are other shades of silver. So there's a big range.
- Like metallic silver. - That's right.
If you want a pearly one,
this one, My Car Silver, should be good.
This one? My Car Silver.
- You said you wanted red earlier. - Yes.
Then paint it gold first.
Then add a layer of clear red.
- The red shade will look vibrant. - I like that.
You can combine these two colors.
- These two. - I see.
- I like that. Let me try it. - Okay.
Hello. I'll buy them.
Would you like to collect membership points?
Yes.
Please check the last four digits.
(He frugally collects the points too.)
Thank you.
(He buys the spray paint.)
- I'll start with the spray. - Okay.
The paper...
(Attaching)
(He's attaching paper on the bottom of his model car?)
(Grabbing)
(He attaches a stick on the paper.)
- Okay. - For the airbrush.
(The mounting stick is ready.)
To dry it after applying the spray paint,
I need an elevated platform.
- I had to set that up too. - Right. You're a pro.
Spray both of them with silver.
Okay.
It's the back side of the store.
This is where people can paint their cars.
(Getting ready to paint it)
The first task is spraying the car.
(Applying a full coat of paint on the entire car)
(He gets started on painting the entire car.)
(Spraying)
(Checking the direction of the wind)
(He begins spraying paint.)
(After checking the paint, )
(he sprays some more.)
I need to add several layers.
Right. You need a lot of thin layers.
It's even.
I must check it after each spray.
That's how I need to layer the paint.
If I get greedy and keep spraying it nonstop,
it won't look good.
It's important for the coating to be even.
You look like a professional.
Bring it in.
You're done?
I must hurry.
(Whirring)
What are you doing?
You're not supposed to do it in winter.
You're supposed to do it in spring or summer.
But I couldn't wait and wanted to do it in winter.
So I used a special item.
My secret weapon.
- I can bring back summer with this. - Yes.
The hair dryer.
You're applying heat right away.
(Come on, dry.)
(Drying passionately)
(He sprays it outdoors.)
That's a lot of effort.
It takes a lot of effort.
(He dries it for a long while.)
You did a good job.
(Before the paint job, after the paint job)
(Grabbing the next item)
I'll cover this part.
(Putting a piece of tape on its body)
Then...
(Rubbing it, so there are no air bubbles)
I masked the car next.
I covered the parts of the car with masking tapes...
and used a knife to expose the parts I wanted to paint.
I sprayed the rest with green.
(Remove the tapes after spraying on it.)
You know what?
- That's the most important job. - That looks like a tough job.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
(Focusing all of his energy on his fingertips)
I bet you have to be super delicate.
I need to cut it with the knife without making any scratches.
- I must adjust my power well. - Right.
(Pulling)
- That's the hardest skill. - Of course.
(Scraping)
I'm making a scratch. Darn.
- Don't make a scratch. - No.
Oh, no.
(Screeching)
It's not coming out neatly.
What a mess.
(Upset)
(Sighing)
The scratches...
(Clicking his tongue)
(However, he doesn't give up and focuses on it again.)
(He manages to remove the tape without any scratches this time.)
I got it.
(Careful)
(Is this good now?)
Look. Does it look good?
Yes, it looks neat.
(He sprays the car again.)
It's my favorite color.
The dinosaur color.
(It's getting painted with his favorite color.)
The more layers it gets, the prettier it looks.
It's rewarding and fun.
(On an infinite loop)
(I just need to wrap it up nicely.)
(Satisfied with the paint job)
I'm curious about the finished look.
(Let me see.)
It's fun to remove the tapes.
- That was a nerve-racking moment. - Right.
- I see. The silver parts remain. - Yes.
(The masked parts retain the silver finish.)
- My gosh. - It came out nicely.
Okay.
That must feel good.
- Okay. - That's amazing.
This looks pretty good. It should do it.
(Looking clean)
What?
I set the overall color in the first step.
Next, I mixed the paint with the paint thinner.
I can adjust the thickness of the paint with it.
(Dabbing the paint)
(Brushing the paint to create a one-of-a-kind car)
- Did you get some stuff done? - You're here.
(Putting it down)
You already painted it yesterday, right?
Of course. Wait.
Let me see.
- Is he your hobby friend? - Let's see.
- He's my neighborhood friend. - How did it come out?
He and I got into model cars together.
I bet you want to beat me today.
- I kept running my motor yesterday. - Okay.
I see. Do you think it got faster?
I won't go easy on you today.
(Inhaling sharply)
All right.
(Whirring)
From the sound of the motor, you can never beat me.
That's a total act of bravado.
I can tell just by the sound.
What? Polka dots?
What kind of pattern is that?
The theme is the Christmas tree.
- On the Christmas tree... - So they're the ornaments.
(Adding the gold ornaments to the green Christmas tree)
(Shy)
(Poking)
(Chan Bin adds black dots to the red car.)
Is it a watermelon theme?
I want mine to give a Ferrari vibe.
It looks nice.
- Oh, yes. - What?
(Putting it on)
(What do you think?)
- Does it look good? - It looks amazing. Hey.
Actually, I quite like mine. Look.
(Trailing off)
Yes.
It looks better in person.
They should give compliments.
- They're just watching. - I already feel so close to them.
- Right. So... - You guys bonded a lot today.
Well, it looked really good.
The picture on the left looks great.
(Ju Seung's and Chan Bin's model cars)
Doesn't it look cool?
Ju Seung's car looks better.
I like his friend's.
(They're ready to race.)
I should time them.
- Let's do that. - Yes.
(They try a test run first.)
All right. Turn on the app.
There's an app for it?
- The records are precise with it. - I see. One at a time?
- When it passes through? - Yes.
It records the start and finish times.
(The app records lap times automatically.)
Here it goes.
(With the tuning complete, )
(it's time to race!)
Here it goes.
(Whirring)
Should I put it on Track One?
(All right.)
(Rattling)
It almost jumped out.
Let's go!
(Dangerously staying on the track)
(It quickly speeds through the curves.)
I see. That's how it goes.
(Swooshing)
- Gosh, it almost flew. - It's so fast.
Great.
- Great. - When I was here last time,
my record was 19 seconds.
(Ju Seung's best record is 19 seconds.)
That's super fast.
- What's the record? - How many seconds?
Twenty-two seconds.
(His time gets 3 seconds slower.)
What's wrong with this?
- He's disappointed. - Gosh, it's 22 seconds.
Isn't that pretty fast?
It is. But my previous record was in the 19-second range.
Here's what you must know. It takes three seconds...
to finish half a lap.
I know what I'm going to do.
I'll clean the motor.
Gosh, how fast do you want it to be?
(Inspecting the equipment to set a new record)
In my opinion,
it could have been the condition of the motor.
The rechargeable battery has to be full too.
And I must insert it right before the race...
and when it's warm.
- Really? - Timing is important too.
It's like that movie, "F1."
A group of people switches parts in the middle of the race.
They work on the car like filling up the gas and so on.
It's the same thing.
(Replacing the parts in a matter of seconds)
- They must do it quickly. My gosh. - That's it.
- It's just like the movie, "F1." - It is.
(It's like a scene from the movie, "F1.")
I should cover up the brake.
When I cover up the brake with a sticker,
it gets slipperier. So it can go faster.
- I see. - When it jumps...
- You reduce the friction. - That's it.
But it gets disqualified...
- if it goes out of the track. - It must stay within the track.
There are only two factors. Safety and speed.
- It's a game of strategies. - It's all about the strategies.
(Adding the fully charged battery)
(The inspection is complete.)
Let's do another one.
It's a single-round game. The loser buys dinner.
- It's a single-round game? - Yes.
- A single round? Okay. - No excuses.
- It will be a single round. - Let's do it.
- No excuses. - Thank you for dinner.
- I already feel full. - My gosh.
(Inspecting the equipment with determination before the bet)
I'm curious about his friend's car.
- He worked on it for a long time. - Right.
(The Ferrari car is still under wraps.)
(Going up against the Ferrari car is...)
(the Christmas tree car.)
Do you guys have the same motor?
- That's important. - They're on the same level.
- The capacities must be the same. - They have the same capacities.
If it goes out of the track, that's it. It's over.
If it goes out of the track, it's disqualified. That's the rule.
Okay.
(Whirring)
(They take their places while holding their model car.)
- It's a single-round game. - A single-round game. Okay.
Is it okay for you to take the outer course?
We'll alternate anyway.
(Their pride is at stake on this race.)
(They won't go easy on each other...)
(even if they're friends.)
- Let's do it on 3. - Okay. On 3.
- Okay. One, two, three. - Three.
(One, two, three. Go!)
- I might win. - What is it?
- One, two, three. - Three.
(Zooming by)
(Chan Bin's Ferrari car is off to a fast start.)
- They're neck and neck. - It's fast.
(How fast!)
(Intrigued)
(Flying off)
- Oh, my. - That's what happens.
Cars often get out of the track during these jumps.
(Chan Bin's Ferrari car is ahead by a close margin.)
(This is great.)
Please! Let's go.
(I can still catch up.)
Ju Seung, yours is fast too.
- Let's go. - They're neck and neck.
- Hold on. - What's going on?
- Let's go. - Gosh.
- Let's go. - They're neck and neck.
- Hold on. - What's going on?
- Gosh. - Let's go.
(Ju Seung, Chan Bin)
- Your car is ahead now. - That's so cool.
Your car overtook his.
(The Christmas tree car overtakes Chan Bin's car in an instant.)
(Ju Seung, Chan Bin)
(Racing smoothly...)
(between the tracks)
(There's no mercy in this friendship race.)
- Just stay on the track. - Please.
- Don't jump out of the track. - Jump out of the track.
It might jump out of the track.
- Then it'll be disqualified. - It's disqualified then.
(Nervous)
(The race is nearing the end.)
The Ferrari car...
(Ju Seung's car finishes the race first.)
(Chan Bin's car comes in after Ju Seung's.)
(How impressive! You made a comeback.)
That was a big gap.
That was the Brad Pitt moment.
(Congratulations on your win, Ju-rad Pitt.)
(Thank you.)
(Feeling proud)
I won.
(Disappointed)
- You can't beat me. - Yours was quite fast.
- This is no fun. It's so boring. - Listen.
- I should redo it. - Come on.
- You can never beat me. - Let's see.
Chan Bin is a long way from beating me.
I worked harder than him.
I'm so touched. I should participate in a competition.
Sir.
My car is way too fast. Are you up for a race?
With him?
(He challenges his teacher, riding the momentum.)
(Chuckling)
- I'm sorry. - Did you hear his laughter?
I heard that a lot in anime.
- He was almost smirking at me. - That was real.
I'm sorry. I mean it.
- He laughed at you for real. - He's the champion.
- Do you have a car with you? - Me?
A car to race?
Hold on.
- I can just use any car, right? - Yes.
But isn't that someone else's?
What are you talking about? These are all mine.
- All of them are yours? - Yes.
Everything on the shelf is mine.
- He painted everything himself. - That's so cool.
Did you paint all of them yourself?
That's why I held a class the other day.
- The taxi. - The taxi looks great.
Just like that.
My gosh. These look amazing.
First of all, I'm using the same model car.
It's the same model car?
Just like your car, it has no wheel bearings.
My motor is slower than yours.
- What? - That won't be easy then.
All right. I'm ready now.
Hold on.
- Okay. Take your time. - Let me wipe this.
- He sounds so excited now. - Check on your motor.
- "My motor is slower." - Please perform well.
Check on your motor.
- The motor should be okay. - Take your time.
Gosh, he's so relaxed. I want to break his rhythm.
- I'll shake him up no matter what. - You got this.
His car might jump out of the track.
- Right. - So I have a shot.
- That happens to champions too? - Of course.
A risky setup could cause that.
Setting it up to avoid flying off the track while maximizing...
- the speed is important. - That's right.
If he gets greedy, he'll lose to his student.
- We'll let go on three, right? - Yes.
- I'll count to 3. - On 3.
- Okay. You do it. - You can do it.
- Here it goes. - We're starting now?
- Count to three. - All right.
- Okay. - Let go on three.
(Finally, it's time to beat his teacher.)
- Gosh, how beautiful. - That one looks fast.
(Please win this one too, Christmas tree car.)
Who knows? We might be surprised.
(No one knows what might happen in a race.)
All right. One, two, three.
He let go of the car later than Ju Seung.
Two, three.
(The champion let go of the car later than Ju Seung.)
The champion isn't worried.
Two, three.
- Let's go. - They're neck and neck.
Let's go.
(Neck and neck)
- They're neck and neck. - They're neck and neck.
Let's go.
(They pass through almost at the same time.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
(Flying)
That was dangerous.
Flying off the track is dangerous.
That's the dangerous part.
That's why it's the most important that our cars jump far...
and land safely.
- Jumps shorten our record the most. - That must give you a big lead.
It can give you a big lead.
(The teacher and student speed up with the jumps.)
(There's no mercy...)
(in this cutthroat chase.)
There's a gap now.
His car isn't slowing down.
It's accelerating.
It's super fast.
(Wait up for me.)
(Keep trying, Ju Seung.)
(Desperate)
(Humming)
(His teacher's car comes in first.)
- That's a huge gap. - It's as expected.
You know what? I think your teacher tried...
to look cool when he grabbed it.
Really?
- He grabbed it like this. Yes. - Like a pro?
- You're right. - Like this.
- You're spot on. - Right.
- Like this. - Like the ending pose for idols.
- He lowered his head like this. - Right.
- I should learn that. - I should too.
That's how a pro does it.
(He wins the race with a sharp pose.)
It's as expected.
- I took revenge for you. - Thanks.
- His car is super fast. - It's fast.
- Gosh, it's so fast. - It's different.
I must accept my defeat. How can I beat the champion?
He's Brad Pitt of F1.
And I'm just a novice driver.
I knew this would happen.
- Ready. Right here. - All right. Switch on.
- He has nothing to gain from this. - Switch on.
- On 3. - Yes, it's on 3.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Gosh, I was faster. - What?
- Let's go. - What?
- What? - What?
- Let's go. - It's slowing down.
(Chuckling)
You got this!
(Intrigued)
Hey, that's a big gap.
When I was a kid,
there were many details I missed out on.
Having this hobby again as an adult...
taught me a lot of new things.
I also realized that...
our understanding of a subject can differ...
depending on when we experience it.
That made this hobby more fun.
I found out that there were competitions for model cars...
- every month. - Oh, my.
I'll find a competition that suits my level...
and win the race. That's my goal.
Hey. What's that?
(Screaming)
Hey, look.
- Okay. - Gosh, you won second place.
Okay.
(The Old-School Me Doesn't Stop Running)
This will be the 1st episode of 2026.
For our first episode, our theme is Try Something New.
We'll be coming to you with a very special episode.
And the Rainbow Club members will meet up again in two weeks.
So that will be January 9.
Great work, everyone.
(Happy New Year!)
(Next story)
(Many happy visitors...)
(stop by his house.)
- Welcome. - You're here.
(A crowd of people is flooding in.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(The rustling holiday vibe fills the room in no time.)
(Grand Project: Grand Rainbow Bazaar)
(The 4 of them come together to launch a bazaar.)
(I brought a lot of items.)
(A generous bazaar opens up on a grand scale.)
(Lifting)
(They're amazed left and right.)
(The 1st floor is the Yongsan Electronics Market.)
(The 2nd floor has the Hannam and Seongsu-dong vibe.)
(This is trendy these days.)
(Queen of Sales Joy takes the initiative.)
(Proactive)
(I'll show you how it looks on me.)
(She likes that.)
(Queen of Sales is proud.)
(A delicious smell wafts from somewhere.)
(This is Moomoo's tastebud marketing.)
(I'll even let you try it out.)
(This is fun.)
- You have to buy it now. - You must buy it.
(A new kind of interactive marketing)
(We didn't know what you'd like.)
(So we got everything.)
(An explosion of fun times)
(The feel-it-with-your-body marketing by Moomoo)
(Could you get me the total now?)
(Should I ask AI?)
(That's what AI said.)
(AI84, in charge of setting the prices)
(Ask me for prices.)
(The thorough manager is in charge of adding up the prices.)
(According to my notes, )
(the total is...)
(I want to buy it too.)
(The donations keep piling up.)
(This is for a good cause.)
(Give me the rest.)
(Gosh, Sean...)
(An overwhelming flood of donations)
(Grand Rainbow Bazaar for the New Year)